import "Catalog/catalog.css";

// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/gb.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: [],

}


export var cards = {

  //#region Table de 6
  "6+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "6+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "6+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "6+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "6+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "6+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "6+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "6+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "6+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "6+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "6+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '6 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 6

  //#region Table de 7
  "7+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "7+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "7+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "7+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "7+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "7+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "7+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "7+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "7+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "7+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "7+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '7 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "17"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 7

  //#region Table de 8
  "8+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "8+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "8+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "8+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "8+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "8+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "8+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "8+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "8+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "8+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "17"
  },
  "8+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 8

  //#region Table de 9
  "9+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "9+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "9+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "9+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "9+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "9+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "9+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "9+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "9+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "17"
  },
  "9+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "9+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '9 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "19"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 9

  //#region Table de 10
  "10+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "10+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "10+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "10+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "10+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "10+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "10+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "10+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "17"
  },
  "10+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "10+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "19"
  },
  "10+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '10 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "What is the result?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 10

};